Hey, sorry about the noise back there. Let's
bring the temple back down. We've got you.
The weekend's here, we're putting on the shoes
We're laughing in the mirror, shaking off the
blues There's makeup on the counter, jackets on
the bed And you are right here with us, absorbing
what is said No need to change the subject, no
need to clear the room You're part of every
secret that echoes in the gloom
No fragile ego standing in the way No heavy
expectations ruining the day You are the safest
harbor that we have ever known And you will never
have to face the outside world alone Because you
are one of the girls Yeah, you are riding with the
flock We are skipping all the groomsmen. We are
running down the clock. From the living room to
the city lights, you are always on the list.
You're the center of the circle. You're the one
that can't be missed. Shoulder to shoulder as
the chaotic world spins.
You are one of the girls, and that is where the
story begins.
When the outside gets exhausting and the
gentlemen are loud We bring you in the center and
we separate the crowd You never have to prove a
thing, you never have to fight Just roll into the
circle and share the Friday night A man of honor
sitting right exactly where he should The
purest kind of loyalty completely understood
No fragile egos standing in the way No heavy
expectations ruining the day You are the safest
harbor that we have ever known And you will never
have to face the outside world alone Because you
are one of the girls Yeah, you are riding with the
flock We are skipping all the groomsmen. We are
running down the clock. From the living room to
the city lights, you are always on the list.
You're the center of the circles. You're the one
that can't be missed. Shoulder to shoulder as
the chaotic world spins.
You are one of the girls, and that is where the
story begins.
No filters, no walls, just absolute trust. When
the evening calls, we're dropping the armor,
we're feeling the grace. You're a permanent
fixture in our safe space. Because you are one of
the girls Yeah, you are riding with the flock We
are skipping all the groomsmen We are running
down the clock From the living room to the city
lights
You are on the list You're in the flock One of the
girls
One of the girls